{
  "Items": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "ア",
      "back": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "イ",
      "back": "I"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "ウ",
      "back": "U"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "front": "エ",
      "back": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "front": "オ",
      "back": "O"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "front": "カ",
      "back": "KA"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "キ",
      "back": "KI"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "front": "ク",
      "back": "KU"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "ケ",
      "back": "KE"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "front": "コ",
      "back": "KO"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "front": "サ",
      "back": "SA"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "front": "シ",
      "back": "SHI"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "front": "ス",
      "back": "SU"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "front": "セ",
      "back": "SE"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "front": "ソ",
      "back": "SO"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "front": "タ",
      "back": "TA"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "front": "チ",
      "back": "CHI"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "front": "ツ",
      "back": "TSU"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "front": "テ",
      "back": "TE"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "front": "ト",
      "back": "TO"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "front": "ナ",
      "back": "NA"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "front": "ニ",
      "back": "NI"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "front": "ヌ",
      "back": "NU"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "front": "ネ",
      "back": "NE"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "front": "ノ",
      "back": "NO"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "front": "ハ",
      "back": "HA"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "front": "ヒ",
      "back": "HI"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "front": "フ",
      "back": "FU"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "front": "ヘ",
      "back": "HE"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "front": "ホ",
      "back": "HO"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "front": "マ",
      "back": "MA"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "front": "ミ",
      "back": "MI"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "front": "ム",
      "back": "MU"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "front": "メ",
      "back": "ME"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "front": "モ",
      "back": "MO"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "front": "ヤ",
      "back": "YA"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "front": "ユ",
      "back": "YU"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "front": "ヨ",
      "back": "YO"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "front": "ラ",
      "back": "RA"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "front": "リ",
      "back": "RI"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "front": "ル",
      "back": "RU"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "front": "レ",
      "back": "RE"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "front": "ロ",
      "back": "RO"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "front": "ワ",
      "back": "WA"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "front": "ヲ",
      "back": "WO"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "front": "ン",
      "back": "N"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "front": "ガ",
      "back": "GA"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "front": "ギ",
      "back": "GI"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "front": "グ",
      "back": "GU"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "front": "ゲ",
      "back": "GE"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "front": "ゴ",
      "back": "GO"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "front": "ザ",
      "back": "ZA"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "front": "ジ",
      "back": "JI"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "front": "ズ",
      "back": "ZU"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "front": "ゼ",
      "back": "ZE"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "front": "ゾ",
      "back": "ZO"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "front": "ダ",
      "back": "DA"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "front": "ヂ",
      "back": "JI"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "front": "ヅ",
      "back": "DZU"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "front": "デ",
      "back": "DE"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "front": "ド",
      "back": "DO"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "front": "バ",
      "back": "BA"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "front": "ビ",
      "back": "BI"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "front": "ブ",
      "back": "BU"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "front": "ベ",
      "back": "BE"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "front": "ボ",
      "back": "BO"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "front": "パ",
      "back": "PA"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "front": "ピ",
      "back": "PI"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "front": "プ",
      "back": "PU"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "front": "ペ",
      "back": "PE"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "front": "ポ",
      "back": "PO"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "front": "キャ",
      "back": "KYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "front": "キュ",
      "back": "KYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "front": "キョ",
      "back": "KYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "front": "シャ",
      "back": "SHA"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "front": "シュ",
      "back": "SHU"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "front": "ショ",
      "back": "SHO"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "front": "チャ",
      "back": "CHA"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "front": "チュ",
      "back": "CHU"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "front": "チョ",
      "back": "CHO"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "front": "ニャ",
      "back": "NYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "front": "ニュ",
      "back": "NYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "front": "ニョ",
      "back": "NYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "front": "ヒャ",
      "back": "HYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "front": "ヒュ",
      "back": "HYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "front": "ヒョ",
      "back": "HYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "front": "ミャ",
      "back": "MYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "front": "ミュ",
      "back": "MYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "front": "ミョ",
      "back": "MYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "front": "リャ",
      "back": "RYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "front": "リュ",
      "back": "RYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "front": "リョ",
      "back": "RYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "front": "ギャ",
      "back": "GYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "front": "ギュ",
      "back": "GYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "front": "ギョ",
      "back": "GYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "front": "ジャ",
      "back": "JA"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "front": "ジュ",
      "back": "JU"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "front": "ジョ",
      "back": "JO"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "front": "ヂャ",
      "back": "JA"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "front": "ヂュ",
      "back": "JU"
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "front": "ヂョ",
      "back": "JO"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "front": "ビャ",
      "back": "BYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "front": "ビュ",
      "back": "BYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "front": "ビョ",
      "back": "BYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "front": "ピャ",
      "back": "PYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "front": "ピュ",
      "back": "PYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "front": "ピョ",
      "back": "PYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "front": "シェ",
      "back": "SHE"
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "front": "ジェ",
      "back": "JE"
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "front": "ティ",
      "back": "TI"
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "front": "トゥ",
      "back": "TU"
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "front": "ディ",
      "back": "DI"
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "front": "ドゥ",
      "back": "DU"
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "front": "チェ",
      "back": "CHE"
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "front": "ファ",
      "back": "FA"
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "front": "フィ",
      "back": "FI"
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "front": "フェ",
      "back": "FE"
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "front": "フォ",
      "back": "FO"
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "front": "ウィ",
      "back": "WI"
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "front": "ウェ",
      "back": "WE"
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "front": "ウォ",
      "back": "WO"
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "front": "ヴァ",
      "back": "VA"
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "front": "ヴィ",
      "back": "VI"
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "front": "ヴ",
      "back": "VU"
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "front": "ヴェ",
      "back": "VE"
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "front": "ヴォ",
      "back": "VO"
    }
  ]
}